<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peoples-uni on The Peoples-Uni</title>
    <link>https://www.peoples-uni.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peoples-uni on The Peoples-uni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.peoples-uni.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>List of Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/publications/</guid>
      <description>The Peoples-Uni Publications #  Publications #    Heller RF et al. Capacity-building for public health. Bulletin of the World Health Organisation 2007:85;930-934
  Reynolds F, Heller RF. Peoples-uni: Developing Public Health Competences – Lessons from a Pilot Course Module. International journal of emerging technologies in learning (iJET) Vol 3, 2008
  Heller RF. Experience with a &amp;ldquo;social model&amp;rdquo; of capacity building: the Peoples-uni. Human Resources for Health 2009, 7:43</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master&#39;s Course Student Characteristics and Outcomes</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Tutors-and-Students/master-cos-outcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Tutors-and-Students/master-cos-outcome/</guid>
      <description>The Master Module Course Characteristics and Outcome #  Students enrolled on the master’s course site, 2008-2020 #  We report on the 562 students who passed at least one module, up to and including those enrolled in first semester 2020, whose results were available by the time that Peoples-uni closed. A number of other students enrolled, but did not take, or pass, a module assignment.
Of these 562 students, 220 (41%) were female, and the average age was 38years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Online Courses</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Module-and-Course/ooc-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Module-and-Course/ooc-courses/</guid>
      <description>THE PEOPLES-UNI OPEN ONLINE COURSES #  Introduction #  Courses which previously ran on the Peoples-uni Open Online Courses site and which are published under a CC 4.0 licence and could be made available.
Peoples-uni Open Online Courses are short, available free for all, and usually contain 5 topics. You can earn a certificate of completion, but there is no accreditation for these courses. Each one would take around 5 hours to explore and contains links to relevant resources on the web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Online Courses Student Characteristics</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Tutors-and-Students/ooc-student-xtics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Tutors-and-Students/ooc-student-xtics/</guid>
      <description>Peoples-uni Open Online Courses student characteristics #   Starting in 2014, we developed a series of courses to be available to anyone at no cost. Most were developed by Peoples-uni, but a number were developed by others and hosted on our site. Courses led to a certificate of completion based on accessing the resources and taking, or passing, a multiple choice question test. The early experience is described here https://f1000research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peoples-Uni Timeline</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/timeline/</guid>
      <description>The Peoples-Uni Timeline Development #  Timeline – how Peoples-uni developed #  (taken from Heller RF, Strobl J, Madhok R. Online Education for Public Health Capacity Building in Low- to Middle-Income Countries: The Peoples-uni Experience. IRRODL [Internet]. 2019;20(1).) Available from: http://www.irrodl.org/index.php/irrodl/article/view/3927
   Date Event Comement     Phase One     2006 Small team of colleagues in Manchester, UK explores idea for low cost public health capacity building in LMICs*.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statement from the Trustees</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/statement/</guid>
      <description>Statement from the Trustees #  Our journey #  Thank you for your support and good luck in the future: closing statement from Trustees We started Peoples-uni with the mission to provide meaningful, good quality, affordable, online public health education to students in low and middle income countries (LMICs) and built up the organisation organically and opportunistically over the years by collaborating with others wherever possible. There was no traditional business plan and it was an evolving strategy – with this mission uppermost in our minds we reviewed and refined our plans periodically, matching needs with available resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lists of Volunteers and Characteristics of Tutors</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Tutors-and-Students/list-of-tutors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Tutors-and-Students/list-of-tutors/</guid>
      <description>The List of Volunteers #  characteristics of Tutors #  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Module curriculum</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Module-and-Course/master-module/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Module-and-Course/master-module/</guid>
      <description>The Master Module Course Curriculum #  Master&amp;rsquo;s awards were provided by Manchester Metropolitan University and Euclid University as MPH degrees and by Peoples-uni as a master&amp;rsquo;s level award. Each used the same curriculum, assessments and external review.
The Curriculum for the master&amp;rsquo;s programmes included core and optional modules, as in the table below. Students were eligible to enrol in the master&amp;rsquo;s programmes after passing two modules. Note: During the time that Manchester Metropolitan University was offering its MPH degree to Peoples-uni graduates, the requirements were for only 6 modules to be completed other than the Dissertation, and these modules carried 20 credits each</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Module Description</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Module-and-Course/master-module-desc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/Module-and-Course/master-module-desc/</guid>
      <description>The Master Module Course Description #  Peoples-uni master’s level modules #  Note: each of the modules is published under a Creative Commons licence. Please contact us if you wish to have copies for your own use
Each of the modules in this programme are divided into 5 Topics, each with a set of resources (as online links in a resource list with descriptive metadata, as well as in pdf format in zip files), a discussion forum for the exchange of ideas and the exploration of concepts between students and the tutor who acts as online facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mision and Objectives</title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/mision-objectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/History/mision-objectives/</guid>
      <description>The Peoples-Uni Mision and Objectives #  The Mision #  Peoples-uni started in 2006 with the mission “To contribute to improvements in the health of populations in low- to middle-income countries by building Public Health capacity via e-learning at very low cost”
The Objectives #    Provide Public Health education for those working in low- to middle-income countries who would otherwise not be able to access such education, via Internet-based e-learning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.peoples-uni.org/docs/pages/hidden/</guid>
      <description>This page is hidden in menu #  Quondam non pater est dignior ille Eurotas #  Latent te facies #  Lorem markdownum arma ignoscas vocavit quoque ille texit mandata mentis ultimus, frementes, qui in vel. Hippotades Peleus pennas conscia cuiquam Caeneus quas.
 Pater demittere evincitque reddunt Maxime adhuc pressit huc Danaas quid freta Soror ego Luctus linguam saxa ultroque prior Tatiumque inquit Saepe liquitur subita superata dederat Anius sudor  Cum honorum Latona #  O fallor in sustinui iussorum equidem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
